[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "5 / 5",
        "choices": [10, 0, 55, 25],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "4 / 2",
        "choices": [2, 0, 1, 3],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "8 / 2",
        "choices": [8, 4, 7, 2],
        "correct": 4
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "4 / 4",
        "choices": [7, 1, 2, 0],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "9 / 1",
        "choices": [9, 7, 8, 5],
        "correct": 9
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "14 / 2",
        "choices": [1, 2, 7, 0],
        "correct": 7
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "3 / 3",
        "choices": [2, 0, 4, 3],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "10 / 2",
        "choices": [3, 5, 6, 2],
        "correct": 5
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "9 / 9 ",
        "choices": [2, 1, 2, 0],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "10 / 2",
        "choices": [10, 5, 8, 5],
        "correct": 5
    }
]